<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="Aquarium_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>Aquarium</modNameReadable>
    <linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2194463553</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="Aquarium_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>Aquarium_1_0_9_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.9.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>A bit of a large update of the mod.
Firstly there are four new fish to keep in the tanks: Arowana, Cherry Shrimp, Gourami and Angelfish. THere may be more coming in future updates and if you want to see a specific type please leave a request about it!
To house these new additions I made a larger tank, 2x4 cells compared to the original tanks 2x2. This can hold up to ten fish. It can however only be placed horisontally for now, need to find an artist to create a vertical texture before I can make it rotatable. 
I have plans of making a walled version of the tank as well. Either one that can be placed over an existing wall or a tank that can be used as a wall.
Lastly I made the fish move a little smoother more like normal fish, and not flip the texture every x ticks but instead when a fish starts swim in the opposite direction. Hope you like it!
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="Aquarium_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>Aquarium_1_0_18_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.18.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>There is now an option to control how the fish use the tank they are in. Default is now to use the whole tank instead of just using a small part. If you like the previous, more organized positions, you can change this in the options.
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="Aquarium_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>Aquarium_1_0_20_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.20.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>Tanks look a bit empty? 

Thats because you can now select the sand color and decorations of your tanks!
Also added some fish and an option to add a Random Fish to that tank. If this is selected the pawns will look for any reachable fish and add it to the tank. Can be a good way to be sure that newly caught fish from Vanilla Fishing Expanded or newly bought fish from a trader gets in a saftey of a tank as soon as possible.
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="Aquarium_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>Aquarium_1_0_21_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.21.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>Another little update, this time regarding beauty. Previously the tanks had a static beauty-value, this is now instead based on the type of fish in the tank. The tank itself has a limited beauty-value and the rest is based on the value of each fish in the tank. The more rare the fish, the more beauty it adds to the tank.
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>
