<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <AQFishInBagOne.label>Lionfish</AQFishInBagOne.label>
  <AQFishInBagOne.description>Pterois is a genus of venomous marine fish, commonly known as lionfish. Also called zebrafish, firefish, turkeyfish, tastyfish or butterfly-cod, it is characterized by conspicuous warning coloration with red, white, creamy, or black bands, showy pectoral fins, and venomous spiky fin rays.</AQFishInBagOne.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwo.label>Goldfish</AQFishInBagTwo.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwo.description>The goldfish (Carassius auratus) is a freshwater fish in the family Cyprinidae of order Cypriniformes, a relatively small member of the carp family. It is one of the most commonly kept aquarium fish.</AQFishInBagTwo.description>

  <AQFishInBagThree.label>Fighting fish (green)</AQFishInBagThree.label>
  <AQFishInBagThree.description>The Siamese fighting fish (Betta splendens), also known as the betta, is a popular fish in the aquarium trade. Bettas are a member of the gourami family and are known to be highly territorial.</AQFishInBagThree.description>

  <AQFishInBagFour.label>Fighting fish (red)</AQFishInBagFour.label>
  <AQFishInBagFour.description>The Siamese fighting fish (Betta splendens), also known as the betta, is a popular fish in the aquarium trade. Bettas are a member of the gourami family and are known to be highly territorial.</AQFishInBagFour.description>

  <AQFishInBagFive.label>Snakeskin barb</AQFishInBagFive.label>
  <AQFishInBagFive.description>Desmopuntius rhomboocellatus, is a species of cyprinid fish. The specific rhomboocellatus refers to the rhomboid ocellus markings of the flanks, which sometimes gives rise to the common name "Snakeskin barb".</AQFishInBagFive.description>

  <AQFishInBagSix.label>Lemon cichlid</AQFishInBagSix.label>
  <AQFishInBagSix.description>Neolamprologus leleupi (lemon cichlid) is a species of cichlid endemic to Lake Tanganyika where it occurs throughout the lake. It is a recess-dweller, inhabiting cracks and crevices.</AQFishInBagSix.description>

  <AQFishInBagSeven.label>Fighting fish (blue)</AQFishInBagSeven.label>
  <AQFishInBagSeven.description>The Siamese fighting fish (Betta splendens), also known as the betta, is a popular fish in the aquarium trade. Bettas are a member of the gourami family and are known to be highly territorial.</AQFishInBagSeven.description>

  <AQFishInBagEight.label>Arowana</AQFishInBagEight.label>
  <AQFishInBagEight.description>The Asian arowana is a prehistoric freshwater fish that has a long, narrow and flat body. The arowana is often called "dragon fish" because of its enormous scales and long, whisker-like chin barbels.</AQFishInBagEight.description>

  <AQFishInBagNine.label>Cherry Shrimp</AQFishInBagNine.label>
  <AQFishInBagNine.description>The Cherry Shrimp (Neocaridina heteropoda), also known as Red Cherry Shrimp or RCS, is a dwarf freshwater shrimp native to Taiwan. Suitable for both beginners and experienced aquarists, it is one of the hardiest and easy to keep Shrimp available.</AQFishInBagNine.description>

  <AQFishInBagTen.label>Gourami</AQFishInBagTen.label>
  <AQFishInBagTen.description>A Gourami is any fish in the Osphronemidae family. These fish are known for their bright colors and unique appearance. People keep many different species in home aquariums.</AQFishInBagTen.description>

  <AQFishInBagEleven.label>Angelfish</AQFishInBagEleven.label>
  <AQFishInBagEleven.description>Possibly the most recognized freshwater fish in the aquarium hobby, Angelfish belong to the family Cichlidae. Admired for their graceful swimming behavior, angelfish make stunning additions to large community aquariums.</AQFishInBagEleven.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwelve.label>Blue Tang</AQFishInBagTwelve.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwelve.description>The Blue Tang boasts a vibrant electric blue body dressed with bold black markings. In fact, the black that begins at the eyes, traces the dorsal line down to the tail, and circles back above the pectoral fin to create a unique shape reminiscent of a painter's palette.</AQFishInBagTwelve.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirteen.label>Koi</AQFishInBagThirteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirteen.description>Koi fish are a colorful, ornamental versions of the common carp. There are now dozens of different color varieties of koi.</AQFishInBagThirteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagFourteen.label>Clownfish</AQFishInBagFourteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagFourteen.description>Bright orange with three distinctive white bars, clown anemonefish are among the most recognizable of all reef-dwellers. They reach about 4.3 inches in length, and are named for the multicolored sea anemone in which they make their homes.</AQFishInBagFourteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagFifteen.label>Axolotl</AQFishInBagFifteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagFifteen.description>The axolotl salamander has the rare trait of retaining its larval features throughout its adult life. Axolotls are long-lived, surviving up to 15 years on a diet of mollusks, worms, insect larvae, crustaceans, and some fish.</AQFishInBagFifteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagSixteen.label>Cerulean Angelfish</AQFishInBagSixteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagSixteen.description>Possibly the most recognized freshwater fish in the aquarium hobby, angelfish belong to the family Cichlidae. Admired for their graceful swimming behavior, angelfish make stunning additions to large community aquariums.</AQFishInBagSixteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagSeventeen.label>Plecostomus</AQFishInBagSeventeen.label>
  <AQFishInBagSeventeen.description>Plecos are well-known algae eaters that originated in the rivers of the Amazon jungle in South America. Plecos attach themselves to hard surfaces with specially adapted mouth parts.</AQFishInBagSeventeen.description>


</LanguageData>