<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <AQRandomFish.label>Random Fish</AQRandomFish.label>

  <AQFishInBagOne.label>Lionfish</AQFishInBagOne.label>
  <AQFishInBagOne.description>Pterois is a genus of venomous marine fish, commonly known as lionfish. Also called zebrafish, firefish, turkeyfish, tastyfish or butterfly-cod, it is characterized by conspicuous warning coloration with red, white, creamy, or black bands, showy pectoral fins, and venomous spiky fin rays.</AQFishInBagOne.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwo.label>Goldfish</AQFishInBagTwo.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwo.description>The goldfish (Carassius auratus) is a freshwater fish in the family Cyprinidae of order Cypriniformes, a relatively small member of the carp family. It is one of the most commonly kept aquarium fish.</AQFishInBagTwo.description>

  <AQFishInBagThree.label>Fighting fish (green)</AQFishInBagThree.label>
  <AQFishInBagThree.description>The Siamese fighting fish (Betta splendens), also known as the betta, is a popular fish in the aquarium trade. Bettas are a member of the gourami family and are known to be highly territorial.</AQFishInBagThree.description>

  <AQFishInBagFour.label>Fighting fish (red)</AQFishInBagFour.label>
  <AQFishInBagFour.description>The Siamese fighting fish (Betta splendens), also known as the betta, is a popular fish in the aquarium trade. Bettas are a member of the gourami family and are known to be highly territorial.</AQFishInBagFour.description>

  <AQFishInBagFive.label>Snakeskin barb</AQFishInBagFive.label>
  <AQFishInBagFive.description>Desmopuntius rhomboocellatus, is a species of cyprinid fish. The specific rhomboocellatus refers to the rhomboid ocellus markings of the flanks, which sometimes gives rise to the common name "Snakeskin barb".</AQFishInBagFive.description>

  <AQFishInBagSix.label>Lemon cichlid</AQFishInBagSix.label>
  <AQFishInBagSix.description>Neolamprologus leleupi (lemon cichlid) is a species of cichlid endemic to Lake Tanganyika where it occurs throughout the lake. It is a recess-dweller, inhabiting cracks and crevices.</AQFishInBagSix.description>

  <AQFishInBagSeven.label>Fighting fish (blue)</AQFishInBagSeven.label>
  <AQFishInBagSeven.description>The Siamese fighting fish (Betta splendens), also known as the betta, is a popular fish in the aquarium trade. Bettas are a member of the gourami family and are known to be highly territorial.</AQFishInBagSeven.description>

  <AQFishInBagEight.label>Arowana</AQFishInBagEight.label>
  <AQFishInBagEight.description>The Asian arowana is a prehistoric freshwater fish that has a long, narrow and flat body. The arowana is often called "dragon fish" because of its enormous scales and long, whisker-like chin barbels.</AQFishInBagEight.description>

  <AQFishInBagNine.label>Cherry Shrimp</AQFishInBagNine.label>
  <AQFishInBagNine.description>The Cherry Shrimp (Neocaridina heteropoda), also known as Red Cherry Shrimp or RCS, is a dwarf freshwater shrimp native to Taiwan. Suitable for both beginners and experienced aquarists, it is one of the hardiest and easy to keep Shrimp available.</AQFishInBagNine.description>

  <AQFishInBagTen.label>Gourami</AQFishInBagTen.label>
  <AQFishInBagTen.description>A Gourami is any fish in the Osphronemidae family. These fish are known for their bright colors and unique appearance. People keep many different species in home aquariums.</AQFishInBagTen.description>

  <AQFishInBagEleven.label>Angelfish</AQFishInBagEleven.label>
  <AQFishInBagEleven.description>Possibly the most recognized freshwater fish in the aquarium hobby, Angelfish belong to the family Cichlidae. Admired for their graceful swimming behavior, angelfish make stunning additions to large community aquariums.</AQFishInBagEleven.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwelve.label>Blue Tang</AQFishInBagTwelve.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwelve.description>The Blue Tang boasts a vibrant electric blue body dressed with bold black markings. In fact, the black that begins at the eyes, traces the dorsal line down to the tail, and circles back above the pectoral fin to create a unique shape reminiscent of a painter's palette.</AQFishInBagTwelve.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirteen.label>Koi</AQFishInBagThirteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirteen.description>Koi fish are a colorful, ornamental versions of the common carp. There are now dozens of different color varieties of koi.</AQFishInBagThirteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagFourteen.label>Clownfish</AQFishInBagFourteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagFourteen.description>Bright orange with three distinctive white bars, clown anemonefish are among the most recognizable of all reef-dwellers. They reach about 4.3 inches in length, and are named for the multicolored sea anemone in which they make their homes.</AQFishInBagFourteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagFifteen.label>Axolotl</AQFishInBagFifteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagFifteen.description>The axolotl salamander has the rare trait of retaining its larval features throughout its adult life. Axolotls are long-lived, surviving up to 15 years on a diet of mollusks, worms, insect larvae, crustaceans, and some fish.</AQFishInBagFifteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagSixteen.label>Cerulean Angelfish</AQFishInBagSixteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagSixteen.description>Possibly the most recognized freshwater fish in the aquarium hobby, angelfish belong to the family Cichlidae. Admired for their graceful swimming behavior, angelfish make stunning additions to large community aquariums.</AQFishInBagSixteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagSeventeen.label>Plecostomus</AQFishInBagSeventeen.label>
  <AQFishInBagSeventeen.description>Plecos are well-known algae eaters that originated in the rivers of the Amazon jungle in South America. Plecos attach themselves to hard surfaces with specially adapted mouth parts.</AQFishInBagSeventeen.description>

  <AQFishInBagEighteen.label>Perch</AQFishInBagEighteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagEighteen.description>Perch are carnivorous fish most commonly found in small ponds, lakes, streams, or rivers. These fish feed on smaller fish, shellfish, or insect larvae.</AQFishInBagEighteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagNineteen.label>Neon Tetra</AQFishInBagNineteen.label>
  <AQFishInBagNineteen.description>The neon tetra has a light-blue back over a silver-white abdomen. The fish is characterized by an iridescent blue horizontal stripe along each side of the fish from its nose to the base of the adipose fin.</AQFishInBagNineteen.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwenty.label>Flame Angel</AQFishInBagTwenty.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwenty.description>The Flame Angelfish is a flashy addition to many aquariums. One of the most popular of the dwarf angelfish, the Flame Angelfish is a bold red/orange color with vertical black stripes highlighting the body and horizontal black stripes along the caudal portions of the blue-tipped dorsal and anal fins.</AQFishInBagTwenty.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentyone.label>Redbelly Piranha</AQFishInBagTwentyone.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentyone.description>The red-bellied piranha has a popular reputation as a ferocious predator, despite being primarily a scavenger. As their name suggests, red-bellied piranhas have a reddish tinge to the belly when fully grown, although juveniles are a silver color with darker spots.</AQFishInBagTwentyone.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentytwo.label>Emperor Angelfish</AQFishInBagTwentytwo.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentytwo.description>The adult Emperor Angelfish, also called the Imperator Angelfish, has a bold, blue body covered with bright yellow horizontal stripes culminating in a bright yellow to orange caudal fin. A striking blue-black mask covers the eyes and a similarly-colored vertical band extends from the pectoral fin two-thirds of the way up the body.</AQFishInBagTwentytwo.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentythree.label>Mantis Shrimp</AQFishInBagTwentythree.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentythree.description>Called "sea locusts" by ancient Assyrians, "prawn killers" in Australia, and now sometimes referred to as "thumb splitters"—because of the animal's ability to inflict painful gashes if handled incautiously. Mantis shrimps have powerful claws that are used to attack and kill prey by spearing, stunning, or dismembering.</AQFishInBagTwentythree.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentyfour.label>Celebes Halfbeak</AQFishInBagTwentyfour.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentyfour.description>The Celebes Half Beak is a very active schooling fish belonging to the Hemirhamphidae family. Males of this species have very colorful fins and a black lobe on the lower jaw. Females have less color in the fins and have a red or uncolored lobe.</AQFishInBagTwentyfour.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentyfive.label>Tiger Barb</AQFishInBagTwentyfive.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentyfive.description>The very popular tiger barb is an easy fish to care for and can be fun to watch as it swims at high speed in schools of six or more. It is not, however, an ideal fish for a community tank as it does nip any fish with flowing fins and can be mildly aggressive.</AQFishInBagTwentyfive.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentysix.label>Queen Angelfish</AQFishInBagTwentysix.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentysix.description>The Queen Angelfish is one of the most striking of all angelfish. Vibrant yellow and electric sapphire-blue highlights give the Queen Angelfish an almost iridescent appearance. It has a dark spot on the forehead surrounded by bright blue. The dorsal and pelvic fins are elongated.</AQFishInBagTwentysix.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentyseven.label>Grey Angelfish</AQFishInBagTwentyseven.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentyseven.description>The adult Gray Black Angelfish, which may also be called the Gray Angelfish, has a gray body with dusky blue polka-dots and the same dusky blue highlights on the caudal, dorsal, and anal fins. The face is a clear, pale silvery-gray. The juvenile is black with yellow stripes.</AQFishInBagTwentyseven.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentyeight.label>Japanese Angelfish</AQFishInBagTwentyeight.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentyeight.description>The Japanese Pygmy Angelfish, is one of the most highly prized and desired fish species in the aquarium trade. Found off the coasts of Japan, the Interruptus Angel exhibits vibrant shades of pink and purple, littered with speckled blue dots creating one of the most visually appealing and exciting fish available for purchase.</AQFishInBagTwentyeight.description>

  <AQFishInBagTwentynine.label>Blue Marlin</AQFishInBagTwentynine.label>
  <AQFishInBagTwentynine.description>The blue marlin, one of the largest and most beautiful fish in the ocean, spends most of its life far out at sea. This is a genetically modified version, more fit for aquariums.</AQFishInBagTwentynine.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirty.label>Black Marlin</AQFishInBagThirty.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirty.description>The black marlin, one of the largest and possibly the fastest fish in the ocean reaching speeds of up to 129 kph or 80 mph. This is a genetically modified version, more fit for aquariums.</AQFishInBagThirty.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtyone.label>Ripsaw Catfish</AQFishInBagThirtyone.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtyone.description>The Ripsaw Catfish is known from lakes, rivers, and streams with muddy or sandy substrates. This hefty, characterful bottom-dweller requires a very spacious aquarium with a soft sand substrate.</AQFishInBagThirtyone.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtytwo.label>Long-Snouted Seahorse</AQFishInBagThirtytwo.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtytwo.description>Also known as the Spiny Seahorse, the Long-snouted Seahorse is recognisable by the fleshy mane on its neck and back. They live in shallow coastal waters and are pretty poor swimmers, relying on their prehensile tail to cling onto seaweed and seagrass to stop themselves being swept away.</AQFishInBagThirtytwo.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtythree.label>Zebra Moray Eel</AQFishInBagThirtythree.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtythree.description>The Zebra Moray Eel is an eyecatching and extremely docile species that derives its name from the bold pattern of bars on its body. The Zebra Moray Eel is an ideal moray for the community fish tank.</AQFishInBagThirtythree.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtyfour.label>Green Moray Eel</AQFishInBagThirtyfour.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtyfour.description>The green moray eel has one long dorsal fin that extends down the entire length of its body and connects to a second fin, the caudal fin. Their faces have two nostrils, made visible by two small openings. On their upper jaw, moray eels have two full rows of teeth, while on the bottom there is just a single row of teeth.</AQFishInBagThirtyfour.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtyfive.label>Moon Jellyfish</AQFishInBagThirtyfive.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtyfive.description>Though the moon jelly lives throughout the epipelagic zone, it is most commonly found near the coast and in upwelling areas, where its prey occurs in higher concentrations. This species is not a very strong swimmer, so they are often found on beaches after strong storms or tides that push them onshore.</AQFishInBagThirtyfive.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtysix.label>Shiny Guppy</AQFishInBagThirtysix.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtysix.description>The guppy also known as millionfish and rainbow fish, is one of the world's most widely distributed tropical fish and one of the most popular freshwater aquarium fish species. It is a member of the family Poeciliidae and, like almost all American members of the family, is live-bearing.</AQFishInBagThirtysix.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtyseven.label>Ribbon Eel</AQFishInBagThirtyseven.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtyseven.description>The Blue Ribbon eel is one of the most attractive underwater creatures with their tiny dragon head and long elegant bodies. A favorite subject for underwater photographers and an aquarium creature best left on the reef. Keeping ribbon eels is reserved for only the most advanced saltwater aquarists.</AQFishInBagThirtyseven.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtyeight.label>Opabinia Regalis</AQFishInBagThirtyeight.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtyeight.description>Opabinia regalis is an extinct, stem group arthropod found in the Middle Cambrian Burgess Shale Lagerstätte of British Columbia, Canada. It flourished from 505 million years ago to 487 million years ago during the Cambrian Period of the Paleozoic Era.</AQFishInBagThirtyeight.description>

  <AQFishInBagThirtynine.label>Black Skirt Tetra</AQFishInBagThirtynine.label>
  <AQFishInBagThirtynine.description>Black Skirt Tetra is a fresh water omnivore of the Characidae family, native to Paraguay and Guapore Rivers of southern Brazil, Argentina, and Bolivia. This fish is recognized quite easily by two vertical black stripes on the front half of the body and black dorsal and anal fins (the latter can be quite long in some varieties).</AQFishInBagThirtynine.description>

  <AQFishInBagForty.label>Elephantnose Fish</AQFishInBagForty.label>
  <AQFishInBagForty.description>The Elephant Nose is an interesting fish that originates from the Niger River and its tributaries in Western Africa. Its body is mostly black and is irregularly shaped with a long narrow tail and what looks to be its nose however this is actually an extension of the fish's mouth. The Elephant nose uses its trunk-like extension to forage for food, communicate, move through the water and self defense.</AQFishInBagForty.description>


</LanguageData>